ravenwoodfair.com 2012-06-11

# Ravenwood Fair | Play for Free

Last Modified: June 1, 2010

Ravenwood Fair respects the privacy rights of our users and we have created this Privacy Policy to explain our information gathering and dissemination practices in providing better services, applications and more relevant content to our users. By visiting Ravenwood Fair websites and using our services and applications, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and you should visit this page regularly to review any changes.

Please read it carefully, and if you have any questions, feel free to contact us at **privacy@ravenwoodfair.com**.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

#### Information you provide:

When choosing to participate in various activities on our sites and using our services and applications, you may provide certain personally identifiable information. Personal information includes, but is not limited to your name, phone number, email address and mailing address, date of birth, and gender, other information that would allow someone to identify you or contact you. Where you have visited our site from other certain other sites, such as **facebook.com** , we may record your user ID for that site.

The Personal information you provide may be used for such purposes as managing your registration, personalizing your visits to our sites, responding to your requests for certain products and services, customizing the advertising and other content you see, notifying you about new features, enhancements, helping to resolve of site problems, handling and/or routing your customer support questions and issues, and informing you of upgrade opportunities, contests, prizes, and/or special events. We may also use such information for the purposes of improving the quality and design of our sites and applications, creating new site features, and analyzing and understanding how our sites and services are used. Your personally identifiable information may be used in a form aggregate with the information of other users and we may provide such aggregate information to our partners to let them know how our users, collectively, use our sites or applications. Again, we never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.

#### Community Features:

If you use any community features (online forums, creating user "profiles", chat and messaging) please remember that any information disclosed in these venues may be automatically made public. You should exercise caution when disclosing any personal information in these areas. However, you may choose to have your profile page be public or private. In the case where you chose to make your profile page private, the information there will only be visible to you. We may combine the information you submit to us with information collected in other forums, such as through emails or offline, or with publically available information or information obtained from third parties.

#### Cookies:

Like many websites, we may also employ "cookies" or similar technologies that provide additional functionality to the site and help us analyze usage more accurately. We use cookies to save your registration ID and login password for future logins, accumulating and reporting aggregate, statistical information in connection with our sites, and also to better understand how users interact with the our services and applications. You can set your browser to reject cookies, but if you do, some features on our site will not function normally.

#### Other Information:

We use passive tracking technologies to log non-identifiable information such as IP address, browser type and site usage (for example: what pages are accessed, how often, referring/exit pages and URLs) to monitor and analyze use of our services, for their for their technical administration, to increase their functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor them to our users’ needs. We also use this information to verify that users of our services meet the criteria required to process their requests. We do not treat such data as personal information or use it in association with other personal information, though we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information for the same purposes as stated above.

We may also collect other information that you provide as part of registration and administration of your account when accessing, using, or downloading our applications, services and sites. Any information you provide to us will be stored as entered.

### SECURITY OF PROVIDED INFORMATION

Ravenwood Fair is very concerned with safeguarding your provided information. We use standard and commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the privacy of your data from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure from intrusion, and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat our commercially reasonable efforts to ensure protection of your information or use your personal information for improper purposes.

### INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER

Your information may be transferred to, and maintained on computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Ravenwood Fair transfers personal information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

### INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

As part of our regular business conduct, we may share information with companies or individuals providing services or acting on our behalf, such as companies providing technological or fulfillment services. These third parties have access to your information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. While we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security procedures as Ravenwood Fair, we will take all reasonable precautions under the circumstances to ensure the protection of your personal information.

We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal processes, to protect the property and rights of Ravenwood Fair or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any persons, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. In the event that there is a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or bankruptcy, Ravenwood Fair may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including the information you have submitted.

### UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

At any time, you may review, update, correct or delete personally identifiable information in your profile by changing the applicable information in your account settings or, for services hosted on a social networking site, by changing the applicable information in your profile page. If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated. If you would like for us to delete your record in our system, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request if we do not have any legal obligation to retain the record.

### OPT-OUT

You may "opt out" of receiving any marketing and promotional emails from us at any time by selecting the opt-out mechanism contained in an email message or any newsletter or editing your account preferences. We treat each of our consumer offerings individually, so if you are receiving mailings from more than one area of our website, if you want to unsubscribe you must do so with respect to each such area individually.

### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

From time to time, we may include links to other websites as a service to you. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to review the privacy practices of the other websites you visit, as we are not responsible for their privacy practices and cannot control their use of data.

### "PHISHING"

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to Ravenwood Fair. Therefore, we work on safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft with respect to information in our possession. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website.

### OUR POLICY FOR CHILDREN UNDER 13

We respect the privacy of parents and children and do not offer applications or services directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, you may use and access our websites only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to Ravenwood Fair, he or she can contact us via e-mail at **privacy@ravenwoodfair.com** or postal mail at the address listed below. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13. We recognize the importance of safeguarding the privacy of children and encourage parents to check and monitor their children's use of online activities regularly.

### CONTACTING US

To review, modify or remove the information you have provided to us, or to contact us with any questions or complaints, please e-mail us at **privacy@ravenwoodfair.com**

### AGREEMENT WITH OUR PRIVACY POLICY

By using any Ravenwood Fair websites, applications or services, you signify your understanding of and agreement with this Privacy Policy, and to our Terms of Use. If you do not agree with our privacy practices, it may be best to limit your level of interaction with our sites, which could include simply not providing us with personal information.

### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

As noted above, we may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last modified" date at the top of this page. Such revisions shall be effective to you immediately upon posting. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how we aim to protect your information.
